<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="script.module.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL" version="6.4.153.1" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" /> -->
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="0.0.1"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.cryptopy" version="1.2.6" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.gdrive" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tzlocal"/>
        <import addon="script.module.js2py"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pyjsparser"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi, απλοποίηση της ανάπτυξης των προσθέτων που χρησιμοποιούν πολλαπλούς εξυπηρετητές για υλικό βίντεο</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This script only resolves video content from legitimate file lockers without prejudice. If this script is being used by 3rd parties to resolve content that you feel infringes upon your Intellectual Property then please take your complaints to the actual website or developer linking to such content and not here. This script in no way searches for any content whatsoever.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το ανωτέρο σενάριο το μόνο που κάνει είναι να επιλύει οπτικοακουστικό περιεχόμενο από νόμιμες πηγές χωρίς προκατάληψη. Εάν το ανωτέρο σενάριο χρησιμοποιηθεί από τρίτους ώστε να επιλύσει περιεχόμενο το οποίο σας προκαλεί αντίδραση ότι παραβιάζει την πνευματική σας ιδιοκτησία παρακαλώ μεταφέρετε τα παραπονά σας στον ιστότοπο τον οποίο βρίσκεται το εν λόγω περιεχόμενο η τον δημιουργό ο οποίος πραγματοποιεί την σύνδεση και όχι εδω. Το σενάριο αυτό ουδεμία περίπτωση πραγματοποιεί αναζήτηση περιεχομένου.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.kcleaner" name="KCleaner" provider-name="Dalibor Lanik" version="3.31">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="startup">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>http://projects.lanik.org/KodiProject_KCleaner.htm</website>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Clean up temporary files in Kodi.</summary>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=307919</forum>
    <email>dalibor@lanik.org</email>
    <description lang="en_GB">Clean up temporary files in Kodi.</description>
    <news>v3.4 [CR]
- Small fix [CR]
</news>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
        <banner>resources/banner.jpg</banner>
        <logo>resources/logo.png</logo>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.aeon.nox.silvo.notoco" version="2020.12.03.1" name="Aeon Nox: SiLVO - mod NOTOCO" provider-name="SiLVO">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0" />
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.10" />
		<import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.0.7" />
		<import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.1" />
		<import addon="resource.images.recordlabels.white" version="0.0.1" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="16x9" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Geskep deur BigNoid, Modded deur SiLVO, en Widgets deur Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Erstellt von BigNoid, modifiziert von SiLVO, Widgets von Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Creada por BigNoid, Modificada por SiLVO, y Widgets por Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Looja: BigNoid, muutja: SiLVO, ja vidinad: Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">BigNoidin tekemä ja SILVOn muokkaama. Widgetit Mr. V:ltä</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Créé par BigNoid, modifié by SiLVO, et gadgets logiciels par Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Créé par BigNoid, Moddé par SiLVO, avec les widgets de M. V</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">המעטפת נוצרה על ידי BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and והיישומונים על ידי Mr. VLO</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Útbúið af BigNoid, breytt af SiLVO, viðmótshlutar eftir Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Sukūrė BigNoid, modifikavo SiLVO bei valdiklius pridėjo Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Laget av BigNoid, modifisert av SiLVO, og miniprogrammer av Mr. V.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Ontwikkeld door BigNoid, aangepast door SiLVO, en Widgets door Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Stworzona przez BigNoid, zmodyfikowana przez SiLVO, a gadżety autorstwa Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Criado por BigNoid, Modificado por SiLVO e Widgets por Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Criado por BigNoid, Modded por SiLVO, e Widgets por Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Creat de BigNoid, Modificat de SiLVO, și widget-uri deMr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vytvoril BigNoid, Upravil SiLVO, miniaplikácie vytvoril Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">BigNoid tarafından oluşturuldu; Modlar SILVO'dan, Widget'lar Mr. V'den.</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V - Sự trở về</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">Created by BigNoid, Modded by SiLVO, and Widgets by Mr. V</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">由BigNoid原創，SiLVO進行改造，以及由Mr. V製作的小工具</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Heeltemal oor ontwerp om 'n moderne aansig te skep, terwyl die klassieke Aeon gevoel behou word.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Komplett neu designed für ein modernes Aussehen und das klassische Aeon-Feeling beizubehalten.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Πλήρως επανασχεδιασμένο για να προσφέρει μια μοντέρνα αισθητική, διατηρώντας ταυτόχρονα την κλασική ομορφιά του Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Completely redesigned to create a modern look, while retaining the classic Aeon feel.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Completely redesigned to create a modern look, while retaining the classic Aeon feel.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Completely redesigned to create a modern look, while retaining the classic Aeon feel.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Completely redesigned to create a modern look, while retaining the classic Aeon feel.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Completamente rediseñado para crear un aspecto moderno, pero conservando el toque clásico Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Täielikult uuesti disainitud, et luua tänapäevane välimus samas säilitades klassikaline Aeoni tunnetus.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Täysin uudelleensuunniteltu moderni ulkoasu, kuitenkin tuntuen klassiselta Aeonilta.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Complètement remanié pour créer une apparence moderne, tout en conservant l’esprit classique d’Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Totalement revu pour créer un look moderne, en gardant l'expérience Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Redeseñado completamente para crear unha aparencia moderna ao tempo que mantén a sensación do clásico Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">עיצוב חדש היוצר מראה מודרני אך משמר את ההרגשה של Aeon הקלאסי.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Potpuno preoblikovan moderan izgled, uz zadržani klasični Aeon osjećaj.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Teljesen áttervezett modern kinézet, de megtartva a klasszikus Aeon érzetet.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Endurhannað nútímalegt útlit í anda Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Completamente ridisegnato per creare un look moderno, mantenendo la consueta qualità Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">고전적인 Aeon 느낌을 유지하면서 현대적인 모습으로 완전히 다시 디자인하여 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Pilnai atnaujinta, kad sukurtų modernią išvaizdą, išlaikant klasikinio Aeon pojūtį.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Direka semula sepenuhnya untuk hasilkan penampilan modern, tetapi masih mengekalkan penampilan Aeon klasik.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Helt redesignet for å tilby en moderne utforming, samtidig som den klassiske Aeon-følelsen er beholdt.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Volledig opnieuw ontworpen om een ​​moderne look te creëren, met behoud van het klassieke Aeon-gevoel.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Całkowicie przeprojektowana skóra Aeon, o nowoczesnym wyglądzie, zachowując klasyczny układ skóry Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Design completamente novo para criar um look moderno, mantendo o feeling do Aeon Clássico.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Completamente redesenhado para criar um visual moderno enquanto retém o toque clássico Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Complet reproiectat pentru a crea o înfățișare modernă, dar totuși păstrând atmosfera clasică Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Полностью переработан, чтобы создать современный облик, сохраняя при этом классическое чувство Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Kompletne prepracovaný dizajn s moderným vzhľadom pri zachovaní klasického štýlu Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Totalt omarbetad för att skapa ett modernt utseende, samtidigt som man behåller den klassiska Aeon-känslan.</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">การออกแบบใหม่หมดจด เพื่อสร้างรูปลักษณ์ทันสมัย, ​​ขณะที่ยังคงความรู้สึกคลาสสิคของ Aeon.</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Modern görünüme kavuşturmak için baştan tasarlandı, klasik Aeon hissi korundu</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Thiết kế lại hoàn toàn để tạo nên một phong cách hiện đại, trong khi đó vẫn duy trì một cảm giác Aeon cổ điển.</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">完全的翻新設計以創造現代化的視覺感受，同時仍維持Aeon的經典外觀。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=210069</forum>
		<website>https://github.com/mikesilvo164/Aeon-Nox-SiLVO</website>
		<source>https://github.com/mikesilvo164/Aeon-Nox-SiLVO</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-10.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-11.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-12.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>[I][COLOR FFFF9800]v7.0.9[/COLOR][/I][CR]- Add music playlist contents for List view[CR]- Fix CinemaVision causing focus issue[CR]- Add Artist Slideshow 3.0 support[CR][CR][B]All updates may contain various changes and/or improvements[/B][CR]For a more complete list visit:[CR][I][COLOR FFFF9800]https://github.com/mikesilvo164/Aeon-Nox-SiLVO/commits/master[/COLOR][/I]</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.hyperion.switch" name="Ambilight Switch" version="1.2.2" provider-name="piotrekcrash">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
		<import addon="service.hyperion.ng" optional="true"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="addon.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en">Ambilight Switch for Hyperion</summary>
		<description lang="en">Ambilight Switch for Hyperion</description>
		<license>GNU General Public License, v2</license>
		<language></language>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.upnext" name="Up Next" version="1.1.3.1" provider-name="im85288">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <!-- This is needed to get an addon icon -->
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="resources/lib/script_entry.py">
      <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service_entry.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Propose to play the next episode automatically</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A service add-on that shows a Netflix-style notification for watching the next episode. After a few automatic iterations it asks the user if he is still there watching.

A lot of existing add-ons already integrate with this service out-of-the-box.</description>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Bietet Ihnen an, die nächste Episode automatisch wiederzugeben</summary>
        <description lang="de_DE">Ein kleines Hilfs-Add-on, welches eine Netflix-artige Benachrichtigung zur Wiedergabe der nächsten Episode anzeigt. Nach ein paar automatischen Iterationen fragt es den Anwender, ob er sie immer noch anschaut.

Viele existierende Add-ons haben diesen Dienst bereits von Haus aus integriert.</description>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Propone di riprodurre automaticamente il prossimo episodio</summary>
        <description lang="it_IT">Un add-on di servizio che mostra una notifica in stile Netflix per guardare il prossimo episodio. Dopo alcune iterazioni automatiche, chiede all'utente se è ancora lì a guardare.

Molti add-on esistenti hanno già integrato questo servizio.</description>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Προτάση για αναπαραγωγή του επόμενου επεισοδίου αυτόματα</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Ένα υπηρεσιακό πρόσθετο που δείχνει σε στύλ ειδοποίησης τύπου Νέτφλιξ για την αναπαραγωγή του επόμενου επεισοδίου. Μετά από μερικές αυτόματες εκτελέσεις, ρωτάει τον χρήστη εάν παρακολουθεί ακόμα.

Πολλά από τα υπάρχοντα πρόσθετα ενσωματώνουν την λειτουργία αυτού του υπηρεσιακού προσθέτου εξ'ορισμού.</description>
        <summary lang="sv_SE">Låter dig spela upp nästa avsnitt automatiskt</summary>
        <description lang="sv_SE">Ett tillägg som visar en Netflix-liknande avisering för att se nästa avsnitt. Efter att några avsnitt automatiskt spelats upp frågar den användaren om han fortfarande är där och vill titta vidare.

Många befintliga tillägg integreras redan med den här utanför lådan-tjänsten.</description>
         <summary lang="ru_RU">Предлагает автоматически проиграть следующую серию</summary>
        <description lang="ru_RU">Сервисное дополнение, которое показывает уведомление в стиле Netflix для просмотра следующей серии. После нескольких автоматических итераций спрашивает пользователя, он еще смотрит или нет.

Многие существующие дополнения уже интегрированы с этим сервисом "из коробки".</description>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Sugiere reproducir el próximo episodio automáticamente</summary>
        <description lang="es_ES">Un complemento de servicio que muestra una notificación al estilo Netflix para ver el próximo episodio. Después de algunas iteraciones automáticas, le pregunta al usuario si todavía está allí mirando.

            Muchos complementos existentes ya se integran con este servicio listo para usar.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <news>
### v1.1.3 (2020-10-14)
- Enable customPlayTime by default
- Do not seek to the end before playing next episode
- Add Kodi v17 compatibility
- Fix logging on Kodi v19 (Matrix) after recent breakage
- Enqueue the next episode in the playlist

### v1.1.2 (2020-06-22)
- Bug fix for change from sleep to waitForAbort using seconds and not ms

### v1.1.1 (2020-06-21)
- Avoid conflict with external players
- Restore "Ignore Playlist" option
- Fix a known Kodi bug related to displaying hours
- Improvements to endtime visualization
- New translations for Hindi and Romanian
- Translation updates to Hungarian and Spanish

### v1.1.0 (2020-01-17)
- Add notification_offset for Netflix add-on
- Fix various runtime exceptions
- Implement new settings
- Implement new developer mode
- Show current time and next endtime in notification
- New translations for Brazilian, Czech, Greek, Japanese, Korean
- New translations for Russian, Slovak, Spanish, Swedish
- Translation updates to Croatian, French, German, Hungarian, Italian, Polish
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/upnext-settings.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/upnext-developer.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.osmosis" name="OSMOSIS" version="1.3.16" provider-name="Stereodruid, Maven, gismo112">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" />
		<import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.2" />
		<import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.7"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.18.4" />
		<import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.fuzzywuzzy" version="0.17.0"  optional="true"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>audio video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Generates Strm files form streams that can be scraped to the library</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Generate Strm files from Kodi Plugins,that can be scraped to the library. Supported content: Movies, TV-Shows, Music.[CR][CR]Attention: This addon uses the TVDb API (https://api.thetvdb.com) to search for episode data, if necessary.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB"></disclaimer>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Erstellt Strm-Dateien die mit einem Scraper zur Datenbank hinzugefügt werden können.</summary>
		<description lang="de_DE">Erstellt Strm-Dateien die von Kodi-Plugins bereitgestellt werden wie zB Youtube, die mit einem Scraper zur Datenbank hinzugefügt werden können. Unterstützte Formate: Serien, Filme und Musik.[CR][CR]Hinweis: Dieses Addon verwendet die TVDb API (https://api.thetvdb.com), um nach Episodendaten zu suchen, wenn nötig.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE"></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3</license>
		<forum>https://www.kodinerds.net/index.php/Thread/53307-Beta-Version-OSMOSIS-Streams-zur-DB-hinzuf%C3%BCgen/?postID=328166#post327429
		</forum>
		<website>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCFC6pKk0cshN1sG15FEO5TQ</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/stereodruid/OSMOSIS</source>
		<news></news>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/media/fanart.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<language>en de</language>
		<reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.notoco.univPrivate" name="Notoco Univ Repo PRIVATE" version="1.1" provider-name="notoco">
		<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Notoco Univ Repo">
			<dir>
				<info>https://github.com/notoco/univPrivate/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
				<checksum>https://github.com/notoco/univPrivate/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
				<datadir zip="true">https://github.com/notoco/univPrivate/raw/master/zip</datadir>
			</dir>
		</extension>
		<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
			<summary>Notoco Univ Repo PRYWATNE</summary>
			<description>Repozytorium prywatne - zawiera wersje bibliotek i dodatków do kodi, które U MNIE I DLA MNIE lepiej działają w obniżonych wersjach, bądź są nadpisywane przez inne repozytoria.
Absolutnie nie używać!
Repozytorium tylko dla konkretnej konfiguracji kodi, występującej na sprzęcie którego używam.
NIE UŻYWAĆ - może się rozpocząć piekło zależności.</description>
			<platform>all</platform>
			<assets>
				<icon>icon.png</icon>
			</assets>
		</extension>
	</addon>
</addons>
